Return of the King is the longest book and the longest movie in the trilogy. It's four and a half hours long
So it's the kind of movie you only watch once
Every month but let's say you can't watch it right now because you have life-threatening surgery in 20 minutes
Don't worry mate. I got this
Pretty sick while I'm recording this guy. So this might sound weird. This is a follow-up to my garbage
Retrospective you can still watch it as a standalone video
If you for some reason hate the previous three books, although maybe consider psychiatric
Hospitalization also while I was away on vacation. I thought this is an excellent time to finally read The Silmarillion
Obviously I didn't but what an excellent time that was
returned of the wait
That Doesn't make any sense he is crowned at the end the title should be the brand new king the movie starts with Smeagol fishing with
His cousin they failed to catch anything and go home down down
hurr hurr hurr hurr
His cousin finds a ring Smeagol says give it to me as a birthday present
The cousin reminds him that he got him a USB stick, which is a terrible birthday present
So Smeagol kills him then gets thrown out of society
They blame the sobrincide but the real reason is because he has a weird voice
So he moved to a cave and became a makeup artist
And then like real life was promptly replaced by CGI currently for Hobby team one Frodo has been kidnapped and wait
No,wow, they are way further ahead in the book. The movies has them chillin in some ruins
Then at night Gollum talks loudly about strangling them to death,Sam
Disagrees with this but Frodo tells him not to kink shame and the seeds of divide have been
Planted the other points of view finally meets up in the newly-opened
Isengard water park time to question Saruman,Saruman,Theoden King
Let's discuss. Peace. Let's return to status quo.Fuck off,Cunt!Rude!
What do you want then Gandalf?
Eh,I Don't Know,I Just Got here,What Have You Got?
Solo shows him the Palantir
The Palantir Are walkie-talkies. That's it. These books were written in the 40s when?
Walkie-talkies were still considered motorola devil
Magic.Saruman staff runs out of durability the King tries to convince Wormtongue to betray his master
While Gandalf tries to convince Saruman to give him information they both agree and cancel each other out
That was a massive failure. So they decided to cut it out of the movie in the book
However, hey Saruman, stay in there and don't do anything evil from now on
Okay, I will not and then they leave for the Helm's Deep afterparty
Rowan is a barbershop that night Pippin grabs the Palantir and calls up the Dark Lord you
are on with sauron
That supposed to mean
Is this a prank call? I'll find you while trying to call the number back Sauran accidentally sends a picture of his next target
Gandalf tells the rest of the crew that his new target is ministery and they're all like, yeah
We know it's but literally the only place he can attack Sarang takes prank calls extremely seriously
So peeping us to join Gandalf in traveling to Gondor and talk to the steward of gondor
Meanwhile random elfs are out on a stroll in a forest and the mother flipping
Rhinoceros tells heir Smith junior. She's expecting inner Smith jr. Jr. So she runs to her father, man, filly
Reforged the sword or I'll be Jetta me Kara Gore's so elrom. Does that side note?
I thought this was the only Academy Award winner in this movie then I remember Kate Blanchette
Ruins everything in this short sin. That would have been such a great movie. Trivia Gandalf and Pippin rich Minas Tirith
You might think it's mighty but it's only a model heaven. Don't say anything because he knows nothing
Hey Stewart, my only son is dead
Eragon is trying to usurp me and a 50 year old named Frodo has the ring of power
How did you illegal Palantir wiretapping Pippin volunteers to join Gondor and thus to vs. Yes immediately
because he knows everything so he knows that Pippin has killed a cave troll defeated a powerful wizard and once
820 portions of bread he should probably roam this place Gandalf says the title
Good job. Gondor is going through a bad time. They decided to build a city in front of a loud dark volcano
So no one is buying real estate and the economy is in the shit's they tried to solve this by planting one plant
But it's not blooming because they don't have a king. That doesn't make any sense. The truth is hiring a professional
Gardener is too expensive to take care of just one tree
It's a noble lie team Frodo sees the city from shadow war and Frodo is drawn in by the loot
System then a nuclear accident happens inside the city so they have to evacuate
Mordor Politburo trying to cover this up would make an excellent
Miniseries gang Frodo continues to walk up a path. That's not wheelchair accessible
Or knowing how brutal the orcish world this maybe it is while they are climbing Gollum comments
Hey
You know how I've been calling during my precious and try to kill you before
Sam is probably worse than me make sense things Frodo. Then Sam stupidly says hey proto
Do you need any help carrying that thing and what Frodo hears is?
Tom gonna getcha, and throw you off this cliff like I did with Gandalf. Yes, it was me
I'm a fire monster then later at night
Or day pretty hard to tell in these parts Gollum frame Sam
Frodo immediately believes Sam ate bread. We all know why he thinks he did it
But doesn't say it because the ring hasn't made him rude
Gandalf knows the giant battle is coming. Otherwise wouldn't make any sense story wise so they need to contact. Rohan
And they can only do that with pyres because they haven't invented the windows phone
They did it this scene is so fantastic, but why was there no failsafe?
Imagine having to move an entire army because some drunk guy tripped with the torch condor is calling parade
This better not be a prank pyre. Rohan moves looks cool
but a lot of horses had problems getting employment after this movie they set up camp in front of a
Rectangle hole in a mountain that they spooky sound effects whenever you look at it according to The Silmarillion
There's actually a guy named maker on the corner making these sounds at night a mysterious stranger shows up to the camp
Aragorn Ivory forged the sword. Yes, you did that in the first book. I got it right here
What a glitch in the matrix
this sword proves that Aragorn is the
Descendent of the numa numa nay a dimmadome and the rightful king of Gondor Elrond is like you are outnumbered
Forty to one and when you have a problem who you gonna call
Ghostbusters, no dis ghost that doesn't make any see at wedding meanwhile in Ostia
Wow, it sure is great that we are completely protected if the attack from the north
Ah, when did they work Lord marine engineering? This is unfair. Ah, they have leather dragons
This is super unfair for a mere almost dice, but he returns to Ministry Father Faramir
I need you to go on a suicide mission. I can't do that. Your brother went on a suicide mission first thing
He did in the first book. God, dammit
Then he asks Pippen if he knows any songs and he starts singing pretty fly for a white guy personally. I'm rooting for him
I think he's gonna pull this off. Ah, that was fast. Ah, my first son's brother is dead
and then the Stuart goes mad just as the orcs arrived how very inconvenient
Team heroin addicts have made it to Cape to Mordor
There is spider web everywhere obviously from small spiders because giant spiders flap giant weapon
but through the search syndrome because all spiders are scary and you know it but he falls over and
That's when he sees
Sure lub who is a total Miller. This is Tolkien's real vision. Shut up
It makes sense. It makes sense. If you've read the derma Delian rather than he kills colour some discovers
He's been set up which he already knew. You didn't have to go all the way down backing Gonder
They are slowly realizing they should have made rounder boulders and the orcs are slowly
Realizing they should have put their catapults way further back terrible planning on both sides
Seemed to enough men are having a spooky time. Hello. I'm the only ghost with lungs therefore
I am king before you say anything. We've been here for
3,000 years
We've heard all the ghosts puns don't even try when I protect Condor for me. Sure
Boo-yah, you're a dead man. Someone had to collect all these skulls and put him in a pool or something
Then the king comes out and apologizes because he realizes he also made upon with when he said dead men
It's just hard to be around dead people then they hijack some boats not shown
How can a welcome water stay on in the White City?
The orcs are shooting fireballs against the Tirith not super effective against the stone city
But it's visually appealing and it inspires the Stewart set fire to his son Wade steered his life
But is not Boromir Pippin runs out fine. Gandalf picks him all night
The two quickly right two blocks. Oh
Shit Dark Souls fights can't we win?
Gondor is lost unless unless
Unless the most epic moment in film history, which happened right now
Nah see didn't
The row row him arrives oh
Shit guys, it's happening. It's happening. Are you ready? Are you ready?
I decided to cut it out to remind you all that we are not friends. The orcs ability says yay
Oh noes the elephant Maori show up to fight the horse Scandinavians. That's not how you fight elephants
Did you not bring my sis? The steward is covering himself in lighter fluid. It's also splashing on Faramir, but he's so tired
He doesn't even care Gandalf storms in Stewart. Stop
You are right Kendall. Ah, fuck. I dropped it faranoush death wouldn't be badass enough
So Pippin saves him the steward realized his son is alive. And this is gonna be such not good conversation
He should just let the fire consume him in the mountains Frodo has fallen asleep in his spider
Sleeping bag and he's such a heavy sleeper. He doesn't wake up when Sam steals the ring
It's use it for evil things then work show up to take him guru
Kai's would have questioned why there's a random child here, but the orcs are like fuck it. Why not?
Let's see how the elephant fight is going
ah
The king over horses is ironically under a horse the witch-king then goes in for a kill but a win shows up
I will kill you if you touch him
Wasn't my fell beast was so she cuts off his head and after such a baller move
She's like, I'm gonna fantasy roast this fucker so she's all be gone
Foul dreamer Lake Lord of carrion. Ooh, I bet that even though his skin is completely destroyed
You can still see those burn marks. The witch-king is like okay, rude, but I don't care
No living man may hinder me then she goes in for the critical strike, but no living man
I am you look at upon a woman and he's like, yeah, I know. I was trying to be supportive
I'm the king of witches I try to support women
Oh and then you know with her grandpa King they get married true story you don't you dare to argue
I bet you thought this wasn't even in the book. Okay, but how did he cut the influence of Sauron? Well
He could have used
Today's sponsor no drapion. Let's say a Dark Lord is using a powerful ring to influence your computer
You can protect yourself using neutral pians military-grade encryption switch to a server in 61 plus countries
including Belgium
No Dark
Lord would ever expect you to be in Belgium could he have used link in the top of the description and used code Killian?
Experience for 75% of a three-year plan. Probably not is a fictional character
But you can click link in the top of the description Nord with him this ad was supposed to be in the travel guide
but it arrived precisely when it meant to precisely like the
Reinforcements for Rohan because now three ships are here, but there's only three people on them. So how do they drive?
I'm so confused explain this to me or league of aunts that
Does make sense. We did it with hit the army wait, there's seriously an entire chapter of Eragon
Just healing people
every damn it Tolkien the European orcs start a fight right as Sam sneaks in this might seem very
Lucky, but no it happens like every 10 minutes. Then this gardener defeats three fully armed soldiers bred for war
Mr. Frodo, I have the ring Sam give it to me and don't say let's make a pro and cons list dammit
How did he know Sauron is probably looking for them? 24/7 not much else
You can do can't really read a book at that size
So the others decided to distract him by making a prank call behold Dark Lord Oh
Youyou got a sword. Okay, okay
I'm killing your fiance. Ya don't bring a sword to a killing L fight, bitch
That's power move cost all humans to march to Mordor
Joe good Aragorn is outside. He's here. He can't do that
He wants me to ask why yes. You are supposed to be my mouth. Go go go go go
Are you I'm taking the mithril shirt
No, we were gonna sell that in my sushi
Hello guys
You uncanny CGI. Oh
You know, what's really uncanny killing Elijah Wood then why didn't you bring his corpse instead of his shirt? Ah
Excuse me
Don't know what that could have gone better
ah
Just surround them but don't place the orcs on the ground that collapses in case I die
Ground collapse. Okay. Some roses are disguised as orcs
They need to get away from them to get into the volcano in the books the orcs just start to randomly fight
Like I said happens every 10 minutes. The animated movie has a race war real shit
Sounds like we need to get to volcano
but Frodo has been in constant pain hasn't slept since he was with that mill so Sam carries him Sam you
Beautiful allegory for a British foreign boy living for World War 1 there's a gate
Good thing Sauron didn't cement that entrance shut
They made it all protests do now is stick house it into the fire and they second now. Oh, no, he's turning around
Let's make a pro and cons list. No, it's over
Gholem survived the fall snuck past all the guards and bites off his finger now that's impossible a more likely scenario
Ah, Sam the heat from the volcano has made my hand all slippery are the ring fell into the volcano
Oh, well, it was only a movie prop Oh ironic how Man 2 would be my doom?
This might seem incredibly lucky. No, if you pay attention you notice that all the main characters are on this side
It was written this way Sam and Frodo did it they can finally take their nap and that's how the movie ends
No, the eagle's show up. Wouldn't they just Floyd illegals there? What do you mean? Haven't you been paying attention?
Hey girls, let's carry the hobbits of Mordor or hey, we could pick his head off and take the ring for ourselves
Yes, welcome to the hotel picking hits off Frodo wakes up and says Gandalf realizes he's definitely dead now
Comes the lord of drinks billionaire things that some people complained about personally
I didn't think it had enough endings. You fouled him awake and then one they died
Ending to throw the wakes up and they are reunited and in three Eragon gets married to his boyfriend
What a twist, but it makes sense
If you're paying attention, and then he says to the hobbits you bow to no one kiss
You're so short you man letting everyone laughs
Eragon is crowned king of Gondor and then he's like no, I drove one it so they asked the mouth of Sauron
Hey who should be king and he's like, I need a good nigga story
So they make the fucking crystal ball ending forward The Hobbit returned to the Shire and it's on fire
Scouring of the shire was cut from the movie Saruman did not stay in Isengard
He took over the entire Shire with 100 people Frodo. Pretty much shows up and says they are
100 people and the hobbits butchered them like cattle then Sam gets married ending
Five-k truants like the best trip ever
All magical beings are going on the boat and fro tell Sam I am going with the elves
To find a new ring Smith because I need that ring back the end a fantastic movie a bit short
I completely forgot to tell everyone where all these films were filmed
And that is the kilian experience
This video was delayed of the delayed but the next video is gonna be a Travel Guide
But it's gonna be different from the last one. It's gonna be more like a story time video. I guess. I hope you'll enjoy it